Guide to the Snedden Family Papers SC1207
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Snedden family papers
1905-1950
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Carlsmith, Christopher.
Snedden family.
Barker, Nancy Sears
SC1207
17.25 Linear Feet 9 cartons, 5 boxes, 1 flat box
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Related Archival Materials
Pauline Snedden Sears Papers (SC0501); Sears Family Papers (SC0523)
Biographical/Historical note
Genevra Sisson Snedden studied education at Stanford University in the class of 1898, and her daughter Hope Snedden studied nursing at Stanford, in the class of 1922.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists primarily of correspondence between members of the Snedden family and their friends. It also includes genealogical material and photographs of the family. The bulk of the collection consists of over 30 years of correspondence between Genevra Sisson Snedden and her daughter Hope Snedden (between the years of 1912-1949). Other individuals of note in this collection include David Snedden, Leonard Carlsmith, Roger Carlsmith, James Merrill Carlsmith, Lawrence Allan Carlsmith, Ruth Snedden, and Pauline Snedden. The correspondence is made up mostly of personal matters and some business between the Carlsmiths and the Sneddens. Also included in this collection are the writings and personal papers of Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith during her professional career. See Box 14, Folder 1 for a detailed genealogy, The Family of Genevra Sisson Snedden.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni; Stanford University -- Alumni -- Reminiscences.; Correspondence.; Carlsmith, Christopher.; Snedden family.; Snedden, Genevra Sisson; Snedden, David Samuel; Snedden, Ruth.; Snedden, Pauline Kirkpatrick.; Snedden, Hope.; Snedden, Janet Hildegarde.; Snedden, Linda R.; Snedden, Loring Bertram.; Snedden, Carol.; Sears, Pauline Snedden.; Snedden, Donald Scott; Barker, Nancy Sears
- Correspondence
  - Hope Snedden to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1912-1919 (Box 1)
  - Hope Snedden to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1920-1936 (Box 2)
  - Hope Snedden to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1937-1939 (Box 3)
  - Hope Snedden to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1940-1942 (Box 4)
  - Hope Snedden to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1943 (Box 5)
  - Hope Snedden to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1944-1949 (Box 6)
  - Leonard Eldon Carlsmith to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1921-1949 (Box 7, Folder 1-75)
  - Roger Snedden Carlsmith to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1931-1949 (Box 7, Folder 76-145)
  - Lawrence Allan Carlsmith to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1929-1949 (Box 7, Folder 147-200)
  - James Merrill Carlsmith to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1938-1949 (Box 8)
  - Hope Snedden to David Samuel Snedden, 1905-1948 (Box 9)
  - Francis to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1919-1922 (Box 10, Folder 1-14)
  - Leonard E. Carlsmith to Genevra S. Snedden, 1920-1922 (Box 10, Folder 15-22)
  - Ruth Snedden to Genevra and David Snedden, 1921-1945 (Box 10, Folder 23-27)
  - Susan Thompson to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 28-30)
  - Nelle W. Carlsmith to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1921-1946 (Box 10, Folder 31-33)
  - William Spaulding, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 34-36)
  - Dale Shoup to Genevra Sisson Snedden, 1942,1949 (Box 10, Folder 37-38)
  - to Genevra Snedden, not dated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1913 Jan 6 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Ella Robinson to Genevra Snedden, 1913 Feb 21 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1916 Jul 26 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - William L. Prosser to Genevra Snedden, 1917 Dec 13 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1918 Aug 21 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Harriet Bradford to Genevra Snedden, 1918 Oct 23 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Grace B. Clark to Genevra Snedden, 1918 Nov 28 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Mary J. Spaulding to Genevra Snedden, 1918 Dec 19 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Kittie Chandler to Genevra Snedden, 1919 Jan 13 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - I.B. Clark to Genevra Snedden, 1919 Mar 27 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - T.T. Spaulding to Genevra Snedden, 1922 Sep 19 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1919 Oct 16 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1920 July 17 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1924 Jul 6 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Margaret Carlsmith M.D. to Genevra Snedden, 1930 Apr 18 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - F.T. Spaulding to Genevra Snedden, 1933 Apr 21 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1935 Sept 19 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Kathleen Hefferman to Genevra Snedden, 1935 Nov 25 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Morrison to Genevra Snedden, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Laura Kirkpatrick Sisson to Genevra Snedden, 1937 Oct 17 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1938 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Janet Snedden to Genevra Snedden, 1938 Jul 14 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - to Genevra Snedden, 1940 Jun 23 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - William H. Jones to Genevra Snedden, 1941 Jul 18 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Janet Hidegarde Snedden to Genevra Snedden, 1947 Aug 18 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Pauline Snedden to Genevra Snedden, 1949 Jan 23 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Leonard Carlsmith to David Snedden, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 66-68)
  - Roger Snedden Carlsmith to David Snedden, 1932-1937 (Box 10, Folder 69-72)
  - Lawrence Allan Carlsmith to David Snedden, 1936-1941 (Box 10, Folder 73-78)
  - James Merrill Carlsmith to David Snedden, 1939-1943 (Box 10, Folder 79-84)
  - Leonard E. Carlsmith to Genevra S. Snedden, 1936 Sept 9 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Edward Sheldon to David Snedden, 1924 Jun 5 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - to David Snedden, 1917 Sept 6 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Carl Carlsmith to David Snedden, 1921 Nov 21 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Carl S. Carlsmith to David Snedden, 1940 Sept 20 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Hope Snedden Finances, undated (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Hope Snedden to Donald Snedden, 1917 -1918 (Box 10, Folder 91-93)
  - Hope Snedden to Pauline Snedden, 1917-1959 (Box 10, Folder 94-118)
  - Hope Snedden to Ruth Snedden, 1917-1920 (Box 10, Folder 119-124)
  - Hope Snedden to Janet Hildegarde Snedden, 1917-1959 (Box 10, Folder 125-129)
  - Hope Snedden to Robert Richardson Sears, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 130-131)
  - Hope Snedden to Laura Kirkpatrick Sisson, 1917-1918 (Box 10, Folder 132-135)
  - Hope Snedden to Roger Snedden Carlsmith, undated (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Hope Snedden to (?), undated (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Hope Snedden to (?), undated (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Hope Snedden to Carl and Nelle Carlsmith, 1942 May 6 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Leonard Carlsmith to family, 1937 April 18 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Leonard Carlsmith to Father, 1937 Aug 14 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Leonard Carlsmith to Pauline Snedden, 1958 July 3 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Alice Myman to Ruth Snedden and Hope Snedden, 1916 Dec 27 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Wedding Announcement (Clinton Carvel to Hope Snedden), 1924 May 5 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Jeannette Monroe to Hope Snedden, 1925 July 14 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Miriam L. Halloran to Hope Snedden, 1935 Oct 17 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - to Hope Snedden, 1917 Sept 17 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - State Superintendent to Hope Snedden, 1917 May 5 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - W.L. Prosser to Hope Snedden, 1918 -1919 (Box 10, Folder 149-150)
  - Katherine Chandler to Hope Snedden, 1919 Feb. 7 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Francis Spaulding and William Spaulding to Billy P., undated (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - William L. Prosser to Keeta, 1917 Nov 25 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Francis to Pauline Snedden, 1919 Oct 22 (Box 10, Folder 154)
  - William L. Prosser to Keeta, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 155-156)
  - Empty Envelopes (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Genevra Snedden to William, 1921 Oct 13 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Bill to Ruth Snedden, undated (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - William L. Prosser to Ruth Snedden, 1919 Apr 6 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Christopher Henry Carlsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 161-163)
  - Mrs. Henry Kuckenberg to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1961-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1-18)
  - Kevin Merrill Carlsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 19-32)
  - Christopher Henry Carlsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1983-1998 (Box 11, Folder 33-104)
  - Hope Snedden to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1968-1981 (Box 11, Folder 105-107)
  - Robert W. Hartley to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 108-109)
  - Leonard Carlsmith to James Merrill Carlsmith, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Marschal Rothe Jr. to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 11 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Edith Jonas to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 112-113)
  - Mrs. Leo Mysing to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 114-116)
  - Anne Smith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1972 Feb 4 (Box 11, Folder 117-119)
  - Lloyd to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 20 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Jan DeRuth to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 26 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Bill Kneass to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 11 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Robert Byrnes to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 14 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jan 22 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Bob Thompson to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 May 3 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Jonn Malarrey to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Oct 17 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1962 Mar 26 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Sept 20 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Raymond F. McLain to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Apr 16 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - C. Worth Howard to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 25 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Bert Meek Jr. to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 17 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Teg Grondahl to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 19 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Wilma Haren to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 20 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Walter Rogers to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 4 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Mrs. Barney Girden to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jan 29 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Autumn M. Ryan to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 4 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Ward Morehouse to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 1 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Marschal D. Rothe to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 45 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Helen M. Doyle to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1954 Dec 10 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Ivan R. Bierly to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1954 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Mary F. Healy to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1954 Dec 15 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Phyllis Michlewitz to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1954 Dec 13 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Robert E. Franklin, 1955 Jan 26 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Joyce Morrow to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1954 Dec 14 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - C. Worth Howard to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Apr 3 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - May Sams to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 13 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Edith Jones to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1965 Apr 13 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Sister Fraces to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1994 May 5 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Kevin, Kim and Chris Carlsmith to James and Karolyn Carlsmith, 1976 Mar 26 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Kathryn Meysing to James and Karolyn Carlsmith, 1971 Jun 25 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Obituary Cards - Henry and Kay Kuckenberg and, 1982, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Leonard Eldon Carlsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1984 July 4 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Denise Richard to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1984 Nov 16 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Chris Carlsmith to Mr. McBride, not dated (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Deborah Seton to James and Karolyn Carlsmith, 1973 Mar 26 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Photos - Kay and Karolyn Kuckenberg in Cairo, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1962 Mar 1 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1962 Apr 16 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1962 Apr 5 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1970 Jan 25 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Mrs. Leo Meysing to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1971 Jul 19 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Clairborne Handleman to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1955 Apr 25 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Judith Greissman to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1971 Jun 9 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1980 Jun 13 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Haylez and Mikel Sampson, Kevin Carlsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1991 Apr 18 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Alison Hobbi to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1998 Apr 28 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Leonard Eldon Carlsmith to James Merrill Carlsmith, 1983 Apr 6 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Kay to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1964 Mar 9 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Kay to James and Karolyn Carlsmith, 1963 Oct 23 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Claude to Significant Other, 1957 January (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Tim to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Kay to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 May 4 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Tim to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, undated (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Tim to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Apr 6 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Prof. A.H. Hastoff to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Aug 11 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Mason Livington Ham to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Edie to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Jul 2 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Jovian Obican to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Jun 22 (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - John to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Aug 6 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - Bob to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Aug 5 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - Jon to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 July 30 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - Dick R. to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Jul 27 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Jan, 1958 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to M.H. Hartwell Jr., undated (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - Joanie to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 May 1 (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Leonard Eldon Carlsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1966 Nov 16 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Time, Inc., 1954 Nov 22 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to American Council of the Inst. of Pacific Relations, 1954 Nov 30 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Mr. Donald Dennis, 1956 Dec 6 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Mr. Walter S. Rogers, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to The Middle East Institute, 1957 Jan 24 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Mr. C. Worth Howard, 1957 Mar 30 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Dr. Solomon, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1958 Mar 28 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Robin Kennedy to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 12 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Amer to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 14 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Oguz Gulseni to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Sept 4 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Ismat to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jul 29 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Edie to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Apr 9 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Elliot Flronson to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Sept 20 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Baby to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Sept 29 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Janet to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Nov 2 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Robin to Kay, Karolyn and Joan Kuckenberg, 1959 Apr 21 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, not dated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Edie, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - The Lee Johnsons to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 14 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Eva Miner to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 20 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 8 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - The Broughton Bishops to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 16 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Katie and Allan Peterson to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 15 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Marty and George to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 21 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Philip, Prue, Catherine and Andrew Miller to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 17 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Jan to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1960 Dec 14 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Dick R to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Aug 5 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - C.L Winder to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1958 Oct 20 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Paul R. Farnsworth to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1958 Mar (Box 12, Folder 31-32)
  - Kathryn E. Lenihand to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1954 Dec 17 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Paul R. Farnsworth to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Harvey Hall to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 May 27 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - University of Minnesota to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Educational Testing Service to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 May 12 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Stanford University, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Paul Farnsworth to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1958 Dec 5 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Elliot Aronson to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1962 Mar 27 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Charles Strother to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Mar 31 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Stanford University Office of the Registrar to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1954 Jun 13 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Wesley Allinsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Mar 23 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Richard L. Solomon to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Feb 3 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Wesley Allinsmith to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Apr 7 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - George Mandler to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Apr 1 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Harvard University to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Jan 5 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Gordon W. Allport to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 June 15 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Bernice Brown Cronkhite and Eleanor A. Ross to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1959 Apr (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Radcliffe College, 1959 Jan 9 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith to Harvard University, 1959 Jan 1 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Jovan to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1958 Dec 4 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Michael to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Nov 15 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Kay to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jan 4 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Ismat to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jan 25 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Edie to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Sept 23 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Sally to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Sept (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Edwin to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Edwin to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Ismat to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Oguz Gulseni to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 28 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Kay to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 20 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Michael to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Mar 12 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Ismat to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Apr 9 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Jim McElhinney to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jan 3 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Jim McElhinney to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Feb 21 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Edie to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Apr 9 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Edie to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jan 3 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Jo Jory to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 12 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Judy Johnson to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 18 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Guido Rahr to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Mar 28 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Bill Kneass to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Apr 19 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Barbara Hartwell to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Apr 16 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Kaytie Peterson to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1956 Dec 18 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Nancy Lowell to Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, 1957 Jan 14 (Box 13, Folder 76-77)
- Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith Personal Papers
  - Family Calendars, 1984-1985, 2003, 2005-2007, 2010 (Box 13)
  - The Family of Genevra Sisson Snedden Book, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Diploma - School of the Holy Child Jesus, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Thesis Summary - Karolyn Kuckenberg, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ethos Article on Father's Absence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Thesis Article - Harvard Educational Review, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Sketches, c. 1960 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Harvard - Radcliffe, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, c. 1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Birth Certificates (Karolyn Kuckenberg, Kevin Merrill Carlsmith, Kimberly Ann Carlsmith) and Obituaries (Karolyn Carlsmith, Hope Snedden Carlsmith), 1932-2011 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Curriculum Vitae - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Middle East - Refugee Camps, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Middle East - Cairo Evacuation, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Middle East Literature, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - New York Job Applications and Letters, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Harvard, 1954-1958 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Resources for Special Education, c. 1955 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Graduate School Papers, c. 1957 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Clinical Tests - MMPI, CPI, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Family Calendars (1/3), 1965-1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Family Calendars (2/3), 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Family Calendars (3/3), 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Karolyn Kuckenberg Carlsmith Publications, 1963-1973 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Photos (1/8), before 1957 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Photos (2/8), 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Photos (3/8), 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Photos (4/8), 1962 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Photos (5/8), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Photos (6/8), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Photos (7/8), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Photos and Clippings (8/8), 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Papers and Letters from John and Beatrice Whiting, 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2018-001
  - David Snedden papers, 1938-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - David Snedden correspondence (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Early life of Geneva and David Snedden, edited by Roger Carlsmith (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Family of Genevra Sisson Snedden, compiled by Roger Snedden Carlsmith, 1995 Oct (Box 1, Folder 4)